V K

VADYM KUZNETSOV

CONTACT

J 0887761154

■ vadimjobhg86@gmail.com

Sofia, Bulgaria

LANGUAGE

English, Advanced (C1)

Russian, Native

SKILLS

- PHP
- Laravel
- Phalcon
- Kohana
- SQL
- JavaScript
- CSS
- HTML
- jQuery
- GIT
- Swagger
- Bootstrap
- JSON

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Professional PHP developer with more than ten years of experience in areas such as the Internet of Things, sales, educational courses, etc. Worked on integrating third-party software systems, such as payment systems, ERP, edge computing software for IoT applications. Developed APIs for mobile and pwa applications.

EXPERIENCE

PHP FULL STACK DEVELOPER Aug 2017 - May 2024

Daxx/Grid Dynamics

Lead Backend Developer for many projects for Naava Green Walls. Was involved in the development of monitoring systems for the condition of green walls and the development of tools for remote control of watering schedules, lighting and air circulation. Engaged in API development for https://naava.app/

Technologies: Laravel, Laravel Nova, SQL, PHP, JavaScript, Swagger, JSON

PHP FULL STACK DEVELOPER Mar 2016 - Jul 2017

KnubiSoft

Developed various applications from scratch. Developed subsidiary applications for the Swedish department of the BCA. Gained development experience using the Phalcon framework.

Technologies: Phalcon, SQL, PHP, JavaScript, Swagger, JSON, SOAP, AWS

PHP FULL STACK DEVELOPER Oct 2014 - Mar 2016

iDeus

Was on the team developing the TesTeachers educational platform, which provides insurance courses for US students. Was involved in the implementation of the payment system, code refactoring and searching for vulnerabilities in the system.

Technologies: Kohana, SQL, PHP, JavaScript, Datatables, Stripe API

PHP FULL STACK DEVELOPER May 2013 - Oct 2014

MobilLuck

Worked as part of a team on the site https://www.mobilluck.com.ua/. Was developing tools for sales managers that helped them carry out mass revaluation of items in an online store. Developed a system for monitoring the items market and revaluation based on the profitability and prices of goods from competitors.

Technologies: PHP, SQL, JavaScript

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE - COMPUTER SCIENCE Jun 2012 Kharkiv Politechnic Institute

JUNIOR SPECIALIST - PROGRAMMING FOR COMPUTER
TECHNOLOGY AND AUTOMATED SYSTEMS Jun 2006
Kharkiv Patent-Computer College